tandyleather.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy - Tandy Leather | Tandy Leather

Tandy Leather is sensitive to the private nature of information you provide to us over the Internet. Our Privacy Policy is designed to protect your personal information while at the same time giving you the opportunity to obtain interesting and useful information, products and services.

When you purchase products or sign-up to receive our catalog or email newsletter, you will be providing us with personal information. Personal information includes your name, phone number, address and email address along with other information by which you can be personally identified.

We also collect usage information from you when you visit us. It describes how our Web Site is used and navigated, including the number and frequency of visitors to each Web page and the length of their stay. Web Site usage information also includes the domain names of browsers that visit our Web Site, time of day the Web Site was visited and other non-personally identifiable information.

Our Web site uses various cookies to enhance your shopping experience. You can choose whether or not to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. Descriptions of cookie types and their purpose:

**Functional:  **

Allow the website to detect your location and to remember choices you make, such as your user name, log in details or language preferences, and any customization you make to pages on our website during your visit.

**Analytics:**

Allow the website to collect information such as which pages are visited, which features are used, and which websites have visited before they visit ours. We use this information to improve our website and provide a better user experience.

**Marketing:**

Tandy Leather use of cookies for marketing purposes is very limited.  They are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging.

**Email Sign-up:  **Tandy Leather will use the information you provide when signing up to email useful information about our products and promotions. That includes products from our websites Tandy Leather, Tandy Leather Outlet and Leathercraft Library. Occasionally, we'll send special event emails announcing sales such as Black Friday, Super Saturday, Clearance, and other special promotional events. 

Your privacy is important to us. You can change your mind at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any email you receive from us, or by contacting us at Tand-E-mail@tandyleather.com. We will treat your information with respect - Tandy Leather doesn't share the information you provide with any external organization or forward third party advertisements. More information about our privacy practices can be found [here](https://www.tandyleather.com/en/privacy.html). 

We reserve the right to update this policy.

If you have any questions about the Tandy Leather Web Site or Privacy Policy, please send an email to tlfhelp@tandyleather.com.

Effective Date: September 6, 2018 

* * *
